I II I CLIFT

San Marcos, TX 78666 Phone: (512)738-3988 | Email: liliclift@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/lili-clift/ | GitHub: github.com/LiliCecilia23

Portfolio: lilicecilia23.github.io/portfolio/

SUMMARY

Front end web developer with extensive customer service experience educated at UT Austin. Strengths in meeting deadlines, creative problem solving, and communication. Positioned to provide unique perspectives on how clients interact with websites and software platforms by leveraging background in customer service and technical support.

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Languages & Applications: React, JavaScript, HTML5, CSS3, JSX, Git/Github, Web/Rest APIs, Node.js, jQuery, MySQL, Express, Bootstrap, Sequelize, MongoDB, Mongoose, Bulma, VS Code, Heroku

Projects

inBloom | github.com/ashlinhanson/inBloom | in-bloom.herokuapp.com/

- Summary: inBloom makes plant care streamlined and simple; users are able to keep track of their plants in one place and easily access information about their care specifications.
- Role: Wrote all third party API code as well as frontend JavaScript to render API data, developed Sequelize Models, debugged app throughout development process
- Technologies Used: React, MySQL, Sequelize, Node.js, Express, Bootstrap, Git, Heroku

Parks_n_Req | github.com/LiliCecilia23/Parks_n_Req | salty-hamlet-73070.herokuapp.com

- Summary: Parks_n_Req provides information about Texas NPS parks and campgrounds and allows the user to make a reservation at their selected site.
- Role: Responsible for database modeling and Sequelize interaction, assisted with front-end design and JavaScript behavior as well as rendering data from API and database
- Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bootstrap, MySQL, Sequelize, Express.js, Node.js, ScrollTrigger, Git, Heroku

Watchlt | github.com/LiliCecilia23/Watchlt | smrodriguez88.github.io/watchit/

- Summary: WatchIt is an app that filters a search for movies & TV shows by the streaming services the user subscribes to and provides direct streaming links to those services.
- **Role:** Responsible for the complete frontend of the search page, also assisted with backend development for the entire app. Developed frontend JavaScript to connect app with third party API
- Technologies Used: HTML5, CSS3, JavaScript, JQuery, Bulma, Git

EXPERIENCE

Enumerator Mar. 2020 - Sept. 2020 **US Census Bureau**

San Marcos, TX

Trained in official census processes for data collection and respondent interviewing procedures. Learned how to be adaptable in virtually any interview situation in order to obtain accurate data.

Customer Experience Associate

Blue Apron

Feb. 2019 - Sept. 2019

Austin, TX

Responded to customer questions over phone, email, and chat channels. Applied critical thinking and problem solving skills to address each concern as efficiently as possible.

Key Accomplishments: Exceeded expectations for the department's productivity and quality metrics.

EDUCATION

Fullstack Bootcamp Certificate: University of Texas at Austin

Jan. 2020

A 24-week intensive boot camp program focused on gaining technical programming and market-driven skills.

Bachelor of Arts: University of Texas at Austin May 2018